Hello, can I? Yes of course.
Thin! Pardon.
It doesn't matter.
What's your name? Cécile, and you?
My name is Francois. I am pleased to meet you. Are you from here?
Yes, I live here, and you? I come from research. What do you do for a living?
I am a gallery owner, I have a small gallery in the tenth. And you?
I am an actor, I play in a small theater.
Ah, interesting! And how old are you?
I'm thirty-two years old, and you?
From Vines.
Thirty, maybe?
No, I'm thirty-one.
You know, I'm looking for a small apartment, do you have any advice, maybe you can help me?
Yes, I can help you. But it's already late, I still have a meeting with a client.
Do you have time tomorrow around three o'clock to go have a coffee?
Yes of course. Will you give me your phone number?
So my cell number is 0623048758.
Ok.
And holds it?
Mine is 06...
06...
89...
54...
42...
61...
Ok. I'll call you tomorrow for our meeting, then.
All right.
Bye.
Tomorrow then.
See you tomorrow.
Bye.